lbsg.net 2019-06-08

# Lifeboat Privacy Policy - Lifeboat Network

_Updated September 21, 2018_

Section 1 Introduction  
Section 2 What we Collect or Receive  
Section 3 Consent  
Section 4 Disclosure  
Section 5 Third Party Services and Cookies  
Section 6 Security  
Section 7 Mobile Device  
Section 8 External Links  
Section 9 Children’s Privacy  
Section 10 Changes to this Privacy Policy and Contacting Us

Hydreon Corporation, owner of the Lifeboat Network, takes your privacy very seriously. We live by the Golden Rule, “Do unto others as you would have them do unto to you.” We want our private information kept private, therefore, we promise to keep your information private and used only for it’s intended purpose.

##### **SECTION 1 – Introduction**

Thank you for choosing to play and use the Lifeboat Network games, website, and other services. The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain the type of information we collect or receive and how we use it. When you use our games, access our website and other services, or make a purchase, you agree to our use of your data as laid out in this privacy policy.

##### **SECTION 2 – What personal data we collect or receive and why we collect it**

We collect, store, and use your personal information only when necessary. All personal information is kept for only as long as it is necessary to provide the services you use or request. The following are places where we may collect your information.

_IN-GAME_  
Since all registration, sign in, and purchases are done with your Xbox Live account, we store a very limited amount of information. For privacy information relating to the Minecraft Game, MineCoins, and Xbox Live please refer to the [Microsoft Privacy Policy](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement).

When you play on our servers, we collect your Xboc Live username and, if there is one available, the Lifeboat username, Rank, and purchases made so you may play on our servers.

When you make a purchase on the Lifeboat Store in the Minecraft App using Minecoins we are given your username so we may add the appropriate purchase.

If you win an in-game contest, e.g. Treasure Hunt, we collect your username so you may enter it into our website to claim the prize.

If you previously registered an account on our server network–prior to Xbox Live usage–the only personal information that was required and collected was your username and email address. We still retain this information so that we may give you access to past purchases. We periodically remove inactive accounts.

_WEBSITE_  
When you purchase a physical product from our website, or purchase part of the buying and selling process, e.g. international shipping for a free item, we collect the personal information you give us such as your username, name, physical address, credit card information, and email address. We use this information to bill the credit card, ship the item to the address given, and keep you updated on the status of the order.

If you enter and win a contest for a physical item, e.g. Treasure Hunt, Twitter contest, etc., we collect the personal information you give us such as your username, name, physical address, and email address. We use this information to ship the item to the address you provide and keep you updated on the status of the order.

When you browse our website, we automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address to help us learn about your browser and operating system. This allows us to give you the best browsing experience.

Only with your permission may we send you emails about our website, new products, community information, and other updates. We will never send you unsolicited updates unless it pertains to a security issue that may affect your personal information.

Support Form: When you enter your information into the [Lifeboat Support Form](https://lbsg.net/support/), we ask for your Xbox Gamertag and email address. We only use this information to respond, if necessary, with an answer, or ask additional questions, to your query. We do not keep the original nor any follow-up emails. The information provided is for customer support only, we do not use it for marketing purposes.

##### **SECTION 3 – Consent**

By browsing our website, playing our games, making purchases, creating an account, participating in our discord server, or contacting us for support, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for shipment, or any other way you provide us this information, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific purpose only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no when you first give us your information.

If, after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at privacy@lbsg.net or emailing us at: Hydreon Corporation 6440 Flying Cloud Dr Suite 100, Eden Prairie, MN, 55344, United States.

##### **SECTION 4 – Disclosure**

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so. Otherwise, we do not disclose your information to another party deemed unnecessary to provide the service in which you initially provided us the information.

##### **SECTION 5 – Third-Party Services**

Third-party providers used by us will only collect, use, and disclose your information to the extent necessary that allows them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. This is includes [Microsoft](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement), [Ultracart](https://www.ultracart.com/legal/privacypolicy.html) (our shopping cart software for physical purchases), and [Quickbooks Merchant Services](https://security.intuit.com/index.php/privacy) (our credit card payment processor)

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy, though the information we have retained from you is still subject to this policy.

**Cookies**

By using this website and having cookies enabled in your browser settings, you are accepting our privacy policy and cookies. You may alternatively disable them in your browser settings, this may consequently impact your experience on our site.

##### **SECTION 6 – Security**

To protect your personal information and account data, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  Should a data breach occur we will notify you via email if possible.

##### **SECTION 7 – Mobile Device**

By downloading and otherwise using our mobile applications (iOS and Android) it is implied that you agree to this Privacy Policy. Any activity and purchases will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

##### **SECTION   8 – External Links**

When you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

##### **SECTION 9 – Children’s Privacy**

We do not direct our websites, games, services, or other applications to children (usually considered to be under the age of 13, depending on the country where you reside). We also do not intentionally collect personal information from children through our websites, games, services, or other applications. If you are the parent or guardian of a child and you believe that we have inadvertently received personal information about that child, please contact us via privacy@lbsg.net we will delete the information from our records. (We have kids too. We understand that the internet isn’t always the best place for them. If are at all concerned about the safety of their information on Lifeboat, please let us know your questions or concerns.)

##### **SECTION 10 – Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will periodically update this privacy policy to reflect changes in our practices or applicable laws, please review it frequently. The top of this page will indicate the last time the page was updated.

#### **Questions and Contact Information**

If you would like to: access, correct, amend, or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Team at privacy@lbsg.net or by mail at Hydreon Corporation 6440 Flying Cloud Dr Suite 100, Eden Prairie, MN, 55344, United States. Please include your name, contact information, and the nature of your request so we may address it promptly.

* * *

* * *
